When your emotions cause you to fly off the handle, sob uncontrollably or seethe with envy, it can be hard to see the good in them.
当你的情绪导致你勃然大怒、无法控制地抽泣或因嫉妒而怒火中烧时，很难看到这些情绪的好处。
It's a common belief that there are 'good' and 'bad' emotions, and that for successful emotion regulation, we must live a life free of the bad ones.
人们普遍认为存在"好"情绪和"坏"情绪，并且要成功调节情绪，我们必须过上没有坏情绪的生活。
This is a misconception, according to Ethan Kross, world expert in the psychology of emotions.
情绪心理学世界专家伊桑·克罗斯认为，这是一种误解。"
"In the right proportions" he says, "all emotions are useful."
在适当的比例下，"他说，"所有情绪都是有用的。"
We can't control the thoughts and feelings that automatically pop up, but we can choose how to engage with them.
我们无法控制自动冒出来的想法和感受，但我们可以选择如何与它们相处。
Vicki Botnick, a therapist in Tanzana, California, agrees.
加利福尼亚州坦桑纳的治疗师维基·博特尼克对此表示同意。
She said we should aim for regulation, not repression.
她说，我们应该以调节为目标，而不是压抑。
Instead of sweeping feelings under the rug, we should practise accepting them.
与其把感受掩盖起来，不如练习接受它们。
Reframe them, not as 'good' or 'bad', but as messengers, giving you important information that you can use.
重新定义它们，不是将其视为"好"或"坏"，而是将其视为可以为你提供可被利用重要信息的信使。
This may sound easier said than done, so when intense feelings make you feel overwhelmed, try the old classic: deep breathing.
这听起来可能是说起来容易做起来难，所以当强烈的情绪让你感到不知所措时，试试经典的方法：深呼吸。
Breathe in slowly, hold the breath for three seconds, then breathe out slowly.
慢慢吸气，屏住呼吸三秒钟，然后慢慢呼气。
For some, it may help to repeat a mantra, such as "I am calm."
对一些人来说，重复一句咒语可能会有帮助，比如"我很平静"。
So, chronically avoiding your problems and negative feelings is not recommended, but that doesn't mean distraction is all bad.
那么，长期回避自己的问题和负面情绪是不可取的，但这并不意味着分心就完全是坏事。"
"We can be flexible and do both", says Ethan Kross.
我们可以灵活地两者兼顾，"伊桑·克罗斯说。
He uses the example of heightened emotions after a heated argument.
他以激烈争吵后高亢的情绪为例。
It can be beneficial to sort it out in the moment, but it can also help to immerse oneself in something totally unrelated and return to the problem later, perhaps with a new perspective and a diminished temper.
当场解决问题可能是有益的，但沉浸于完全无关的事情中，稍后再回到问题上来也可能有帮助，也许会带着新的视角和消减的脾气。
Another way to distract yourself is to change your environment.
另一种分散注意力的方法是改变你的环境。
Anyone that's been on holiday will know that being in new surroundings, free of associations of work and usual routines, can help us de-stress and recharge.
任何度过假的人都知道，身处与工作和日常流程惯例无关的新环境中，有助于我们减压和恢复精力。
If you're unable to get away, try exploring locally.
如果你无法离开，可以尝试在当地探索。
A 2024 review of research called 'The role of nature in emotion regulation processes' found all 27 of the reviewed studies reported positive impacts of nature on emotion regulation.
2024年一项名为《自然在情绪调节过程中的作用》的研究综述发现，所有27项研究评述都报告了自然对情绪调节的积极影响。
If green spaces are hard to reach in your neighbourhood, try curating your home environment.
如果你所在的社区难以接触到绿地空间，可以尝试策划你的家庭环境。
Add house plants, pictures of landscapes, photos of loved ones, or any objects that bring you joy.
添加室内植物、风景画、亲人的照片，或任何能给你带来快乐的物品。
Learning to accept, reframe and regulate your emotions puts you back in the driver's seat of your life.
学会接受、重新塑造和调节你的情绪，会让你重新掌控你的生活。
But if this feels hard, remember: no feeling lasts forever.
但如果感觉这样做很难，记住：没有一种感觉是永恒的。